<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Code of Conduct on PKI Consortium</title><link>https://pkic.org/code-of-conduct/</link><description>Recent content in Code of Conduct on PKI Consortium</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>PKI Consortium, Inc. All Rights Reserved</copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 13:49:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://pkic.org/code-of-conduct/feed/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Code of Conduct for Participants</title><link>https://pkic.org/code-of-conduct/participants/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 13:49:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pkic.org/code-of-conduct/participants/</guid><description>Introduction The PKI Consortium (the “PKIC”) is comprised of a global group of professionals with differences in language, skills, expertise, experience, and backgrounds. Participants include PKIC Members and third parties (non-members). To maintain a professional and productive environment, it is necessary Participants of the PKIC to follow the letter and spirit of this Code. This Code applies to all official PKIC activities, such as meetings, teleconferences, mailing lists, conferences, and other PKIC functions.</description></item><item><title>Code of Conduct for Publications</title><link>https://pkic.org/code-of-conduct/publications/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 10:00:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pkic.org/code-of-conduct/publications/</guid><description>Opinions Any opinions expressed at pkic.org or any other publication of the PKI Consortium, except as specifically noted, are those of the individual author(s) and do not necessarily represent the views or policies of the PKI Consortium.
Authors are not responsible for the accuracy of information supplied by authors or by third-party sources.
Comments Comments are welcome and moderated by the PKI Consortium. Commentary, opinions, and reactions to all comment posts are welcome.</description></item></channel></rss>